<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
	<data>

		<!-- Definition of the report -->
		<report id="report_job_confirmation"
				model="hr.contract"
				string="Print Job Confirmation"
				name="yuko_hr_contract.report_job_confirmation_letter_qweb"
				file="yuko_hr_contract.report_job_confirmation_letter_qweb"
				report_type="qweb-pdf"
                menu="False"
				paperformat="yuko_hr_contract.Yuko_pad_paperformat"
        />

		<!-- Main template -->
		<template id="report_job_confirmation_letter_qweb">
			<t t-call="report.html_container">
				<t t-foreach="docs" t-as="o">
				<t t-name="report.external_layout">
					<div class="page">
					<br/>
						<div class="text-left">
							<b><span t-esc="context_timestamp(datetime.datetime.now()).strftime('%Y-%m-%d')"/></b>
							<br/><br/>
							<span t-field="o.employee_id.name"/><br/>
							<span t-field="o.job_id"/><br/>
							<span t-field="o.department_id.name"/>
						</div>
						<br/><br/><br/>

						<b> Sub: Letter of Job Confirmation after probation period. </b><br/><br/><br/>

						<p>Dear  <span t-field="o.employee_id.name"/>, </p>

						<p>Following completion of your probation period form <span t-field="o.trial_date_start"/> to <span t-field="o.trial_date_end"/> at Yuko Leather Goods Ltd. We have reviewed your performance and found the same to be satisfactory.</p>

						<p>In view of the above, we are pleased to inform you that you have been confirmed to the position of <span t-field="o.job_id"/> at Yuko Leather Goods Ltd. will effective from date mentioned in new contract attached with this letter. Your basic salary has been revised to <span t-field="o.wage"/> BDT per month, will effect from your confirmation date and other benefits will be entertain based on basic salary.</p>

						<p>Your salary will be reviews every 12 months and will be increases based upon satisfactory performance in the position.</p>

						<p>All other terms and conditions of your appointment will remain the same. Please signify your acceptance of these terms and conditions by signing the new agreement attached with this letter &amp; return to Human Resource Dept. at an earliest convenient time.</p>

						<p>In case you have any queries, do not hesitate to reach our Human Resource Officer / Department Supervisor. Yuko Leather Goods Ltd.</p>
						<br/>
						<p><b>Congratulates! This is your confirmation letter and wishes you well in your position.</b></p>
						<br/><br/>


						Sincerely,

						<p><span t-raw="user.signature"/></p>


						<p style="margin-top: 15%; text-decoration: underline;"><b>Attached Contract Documents: </b></p>
						<p>Job Responsibility &amp; Timing</p>
						<p>Salary</p>
						<p>Advantages</p>
						<p>Terms &amp; Condition</p>

					</div>
				</t>
				</t>
			</t>
		</template>


	</data>
</odoo>